Zionists are pushing a new line of propaganda that's aimed at breaking Black solidarity with
Palestinians. They're trying to convince people that the only reason Palestinians are getting
attention right now is because we're not Black. Then they point to the Democratic Republic of
Congo, the DRC, and say, look at those people who've been murdered and nobody's paying attention
to them, and it's because they're Black. And the point of this is to fracture our movements.
So first of all, Palestinian society is multiracial, and there are Black Palestinians who are getting
slaughtered in Gaza, just like the rest of their neighbors. But what's more important is you should
know that Israel is at the heart of the genocide in the DRC, as they have been arming and training
militias in Rwanda and Uganda who are responsible for maintaining the violent chaos to facilitate
Western mineral extraction from Congo's mines. The M23 militia is the primary culprit, and they've
received surveillance, software, military hardware, funds, and training from various Western states,
and especially from Israel. Furthermore, Israel not only cheered for the assassination of Patrice
Lumumba, the first democratically elected president of Congo, but they actually helped prevent bringing
his murderers to justice. They then helped maintain the horrifically oppressive rule of Mobutu Seseseiko
for decades. In fact, a contingent of Israeli armed and trained paratroopers were the backbone of Mobutu's
suppression throughout Congo. Go through any atrocity in the whole of Africa, and you will find Israel is
part of it. From the Rwandan genocide, Israeli arms dealers boasted about supplying weapons to the
Hutu's when the world knew what they were doing to the Tutsis, to the genocidal diamond extraction
industry, or oil extraction, or any other extraction in Africa. If you examine genocide and oppression
anywhere in the world, you'll usually find the U.S., Israel, and Britain are the instigators, and it's for
profit and for consolidation of power. The genocide of Palestinians is not separate from these, and frankly,
it's fine if folks don't want to speak up for Palestinians getting slaughtered right now, but it's a whole
other level to go on social media to explain why others shouldn't either at this hour when the
equivalent of an atomic bomb has been dropped on the most densely populated place on earth. Sadly, people
think that solidarity is a zero-sum game. We can chew gum and walk at the same time. We can acknowledge the
problems within our movements and work on them without deliberate fracturing. What's also interesting
is that a lot of the folks bringing up the DRC themselves have never said a word about those
places. For the record, I'm Palestinian, and I have written and spoken about it, as well as the other
atrocities that have been happening in Africa that have been instigated by Western powers, because it's all
connected, and that needs to be said over and over.